HERI YANTO

I have twelve years of experience in Management.

Currently, I work in the customer service industry as a Delivery Manager, leading 40+ Customer Service agents and several team leaders. I spend my free time learning about Web Development and working on several small web projects.



WORK EXPERIENCE

DELIVERY MANAGER

INFLUX | 2020 - Recently

SALES MANAGER

PT.CITRA LESTARI MOBILINDO|2017-2019 Authorized Hino Dealer

BRANCH HEAD

PT. ASTRA INTERNATIONAL, Tbk | 2013-2015 UD TRUCKS SALES OPERATION

BRANCH HEAD

PT. CITRA LESTARI MOBILINDO | 2011-2013 Authorized Hino Dealer

AREA SALES MANAGER

PT.ORINDO ALAM AYU | 2010-2011 Authorized Hino Dealer

SALES PERSON

PT. ASTRA INTERNATIONAL, Tbk | 2007-2009 TOYOTA SALES OPERATION

TOP EXPERT SKILLS

Management

Sales Management

Customer Service

Management

HTML, CSS,

Javascript, Python

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITAS MDP PALEMBANG

- Bachelor of Computer Science, Information System
- GPA 3,03/4

CONTACT INFO



https://heriyanto.dev

https://www.linkedin.com/in/heri-yanto-201299186/